

SKILLS

English

Time

Organizational

management

Communication — — — —

Problem-

Solving

Technical skills

CSS
HTML
NumPy
Pandas
OOP
Unit-tests
Flask
Python
SQL
Docker
GitHub
GitLab
CI/CD

Soft skills

CONTACT

- Dnipro
- **** +380956574238
- **□** +380956574238
- ✓ gleb1395@gmail.com
- **4** +380956574238

GLEB DUBININ

TRAINEE PYTHON DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Having finished an advanced Python and basic courses at Hillel IT school having my own ongoing pet project at Django, having over 5 years of experience in cartography and 10 years in geodesy and want to switch to Python engineer position.

EXPERIENCE

2022 - Present

Comfort CityBud

Surveyor, Dnipro

- Mapping and Cartography
- Structural Analysis
- Attention to Details
- Data Visualization
- Data Collection
- Structural Analysis

2020 - 2022

RBU-1

Surveyor, Kyiv

- Topographic Mapping
- Industrial Surveying
- Blueprint Interpretation
- Preparation and maintenance of accurate drawings, sketches and records of survey data
- Usage of GPS and GNSS technologies.

2019 - 2020

PROJECT INVESTBUD

Surveyor, Kyiv

- Industrial Surveying
- Structural Analysis
- Blueprint Interpretation
- Creation of 3D models
- Project Coordination
- Topographic Mapping

2015 - 2019

Zhilstroy-1

Surveyor, Kharkiv

- Conducting land survey work.
- Topographic Mapping
- Usage of GPS and GNSS technologies.
- Creation and interpretation of maps
- Conducting detailed topographic surveys
- Usage of AutoCad and Civil3D

EDUCATION

2024 - Present HILLEL IT SCHOOL Python Pro, City **Completed an advanced Python course** covering Flask, Django, caching, concurrency, deployment, unit testing, Django Rest Framework, Docker, Bash/Linux basics, and database management. 2023 - 2024 HILLEL IT SCHOOL Python Basic Completed basic Python courses from an IT school, gaining foundational knowledge in Python programming, including essential syntax, data structures 2016 - 2017 O.M. BEKETOV NATIONAL UNIVERSITY OF URBAN ECONOMY Geodesy, Cartography and Land Management, Kharkiv Specialist of geodesy and land management. Program subject area "Geodesy and land management".

2012 - 2016 O.M. BEKETOV NATIONAL UNIVERSITY OF URBAN ECONOMY

System and Technologies"

Geodesy, Cartography and Land Management, Kharkiv

Bachelor of geodesy and land management

Educational program "Geoinformation